[inaudible]
[door opening]
Good night, brother.
[door closing].
[silence]
[door closing]
[door opening]
They had to switch up
your food because they
didn't know you were going to McDonald's.
So they're getting you some food
from McDonald's. That's all right?
All right. What are you getting?
Big Macs, Quarter Pounder,
they're getting a bunch of stuff.
And fries and stuff.
I'm getting fish sandwich.
Fish sandwich?
Yeah, fish fillet.
Okay.
Yeah.
Let me tell you real quick.
I'm going to have somebody
show you some photos.
And see if you can remember
the other person that
was there at the time when
the incident happened.
All right?
Okay.
Give me two minutes.
I can make you fish fillet.
All right.
[door opening].
[silence]
[door closing]
[door opening]
[silence].
[door closing].
[door opening].
[silence].
[door closing]
[door opening]
[silence]
[door closing].
[door opening]
Good afternoon.
How you doing?
I'm good.
You look good.
My name is Detective Tate.
I'm here on behalf of Detective Talley.
He spoke with you already
in reference to the
photographic reprocess
you're about to take part in.
Yeah.
Okay.
Having said that, I'm going to read
some instructions to you, okay?
At any point in time, during the course
of me reading these instructions to you,
if you don't understand, you
have a question, let me know.
I'll stop.
I'll explain it to you, and
we'll move forward, okay?
Okay.
All right.
Um, excuse me.
As part of the ongoing investigation into
the crime that occurred on June 18, 2022,
in the 3800 block of
Derby Manor Road, you'll
be shown a series of photographs, okay?
Mm-hmm.
I am not involved in this investigation
other than showing these photographs,
and I do not know the
identity of the suspect, okay?
Mm-hmm.
The person who committed
the crime may or may not
be in the set of photographs
you're about to view.
You understand that?
Yes.
The individuals you view
may not appear exactly
as they did on the date of the incident.
Features such as head, facial
hair are subject to change, okay?
Yes.
Photographs may not always depict
the true complexion of a person
and may be lighter or darker
than shown in the photo, okay?
Yes.
Pay no attention to any markings and/or
color defects that may appear on the photos
and any other difference in the
type or style of photographs, okay?
Yes.
You must look at all photographs
contained in this file, okay?
Yes.
After you have the opportunity
to view the photographs,
I would ask you to follow
on three questions.
One, do you recognize anyone?
Two, if you do, what number
of persons do you recognize?
And third, what role or opinion does the
person play in this investigation, okay?
Okay.
Do not discuss with any
other witnesses what
you see, say, or do during
this procedure, okay?
Yes.
And regardless of whether
or not you select someone,
the Baltimore City Police Department will
continue to investigate this incident.
Do you understand what I read to you?
Yes.
Do you have any questions for me?
No.
Okay.
If you understand what I read to
you, what I need you to do for
me is place an initial
on each one of those
lines going down, initial date and time.
[Pause]
Oh, yeah.
Today is 2/14/2013.
The time is currently 1:45.
Okay.
[Pause]
All right. Ms. Burrows, when
you're ready, you can open that up.
[Pause]
At this time, have you had the opportunity
to look at all six photographs?
Yes.
Do you need to review
the photographs again?
No.
Okay. Do you recognize anybody?
No, not really. I'm missing one.
Well, you can't look at
them separately, so what
I'm going to do is, if you
want, I can reissue them again.
You can take your time to look at them.
Take your time. No rush.
And we'll go from there, okay?
Okay.
[Pause]
Okay. And again, have you had the
opportunity to view all six photographs?
Yeah.
Do you recognize anybody?
No.
All right. At this time, stand by
at the Technical Aid magazine, okay?
All right.
[Pause]
All right, London.
Your food is on the way, and we have some
other people from ATF who want
to talk to you, all right?
All right.
Hey, I'm Dawn.
How are you, Dawn?
I'm from ATF.
Yeah.
This is Ted and Dan.
How are you?
Good.
Yeah, you good?
Yeah.
Thanks.
I'm not here to talk to
you about the shooting
that you're in here for.
Do you know what ATF does?
We're basically FBI's better
brother where we handle
violent crime, firearms,
firearms trafficking,
arsenic explosives is another group, but
we're basically mostly violent crime.
Oh, wow.
So during the last time
that you sat down with
Tally and Jeff Naylor,
the state's attorney,
you had talked about the gun
that you had in your possession.
I'm a lawyer.
Oh, oh, sorry.
I'm making sure nothing is-- Hold on.
All right.
When he said, "Oh, I'm going
to go tell her her food's
back," and I heard it, I was
like, "Oh, I missed my cue."
Oh, sorry.
I just introduced him and was talking
about what ATF does, which is-- Yeah.
All right.
Thank you.
So when you were sitting
down with Jeff Naylor before,
you had said that the guns
that they recovered on you,
you had gotten with Devin
and Dion down in Georgia.
Do you remember that whole conversation?
Yeah.
So it piqued our interest about who
it was that was buying guns in Atlanta
and then how they were making
their way to Baltimore because
obviously Baltimore has a
pretty high gun crime rate,
and so we're kind of wondering where all
the gun influx is coming from downtown.
So those are the questions
that I'll be asking,
but if you want, we can just go with you,
and then you say, and then if I have any
follow-up questions, I can go from there.
Okay.
What do you think?
First, I don't know
exactly where they come
from down there, but
when I was down there,
like a gun school, they
go to a gun school,
and just somebody had
a license to get them,
and they get them, and then they transport
them back through like the Chinese bus,
and that's how they get
them back, through the
Chinese bus, because you
don't get searched on.
Yeah, I mean, it's a really good thing
because you put all your luggage below,
and then you're riding, so you don't
really have to own up to any of your stuff.
That time that you went down with them,
just those two, right, Devin and Dion?
Yeah.
Is that the only time that
you went down with them?
Yes.
Do you know how many times--so I guess
who is that main person that goes down?
Devin.
Devin?
Yeah.
And do you know Devin's last name?
No.
Would you be able to
identify him if you saw him?
Yes.
Who is this person to you?
That's Devin.
That's Devin?
Yeah.
And then do you recognize this person?
Who is that?
Dion.
That's Dion?
Yeah.
Okay, so those two go down.
Does Dion have family down there?
Yeah, he has family down there.
Who lives down there?
His mom.
Do you know her name?
Shelly.
And who else lives down there?
That's my mom.
Okay.
Is Shelly the one that
was buying the guns?
No.
She doesn't know nothing about it.
Oh, she doesn't.
Okay.
No.
Who was the person buying the guns?
It was somebody that Dion knew.
Okay.
And I don't know the guy per se.
And do you remember what he looked like?
I can't.
I mean, he's black.
Blackmailing it, Leanna, got it.
Blackmailing it, blackmailing it.
I don't really know him personally because
I didn't really get introduced to him.
Okay.
Do you remember his name?
No.
Okay.
And you only met him that one time?
Yeah.
Do you think if you saw a picture of
him, you'd be able to recognize him?
Not really because I
only did a quick drive
and then, you know,
this, exchange and gone.
So.
All right.
Let's just go through
when you went down there.
You went down there on the Chinese bus.
Did somebody take you
over to the bus station?
We called Uber to the house.
Who paid for that Uber?
I did.
And you have an Uber account?
Yes.
And what was the address of the
house that you guys went to?
I don't know.
Okay.
I don't remember.
A street name?
I don't know.
A street name.
Yeah.
Who gave you the address to the house?
The.
And whose house was it?
It was, I think it was his father's house.
I think it was his father's house.
Okay.
And who did you meet when you got there?
His father and the kids and stuff.
How many kids?
It was like one, two, five of them.
Do you remember his dad's name?
No.
Do you remember what he looked like?
Or how old the kids were?
I don't know.
They were young kids.
Yeah.
I want to say like four of the ten.
And was there any females or anybody else
living at the house
besides the dad and kids?
No.
Okay.
And would that be his father and then
mother would be Shelly at a different house?
Yeah.
All right.
That house that you guys drove to, is that
like an apartment, a single family home?
That just means like one house?
It was a single family home.
Single family.
All right.
And what happened when you guys got there?
We went down there.
We chilled for a little bit.
We went out, partied and stuff like that.
And then I left.
I wound up leaving them down there.
And I left and caught
the bus back by myself.
Well, during that time you
guys bought a gun, right?
Yeah.
So let's say you guys bought a gun.
It was already brought.
Oh, okay.
I just got it from -- And
who did you get it from?
I just got it from Devin Hedges.
I just got it from him.
Oh, okay.
And had Devin gotten it while he was
down there or did he come down with it?
No, he didn't come down with it.
He left and in exchange he got it
from the guy that I told you about.
And then that's when I got it
from him and that was that.
Okay.
And I left and came back down
here because I had to go to work.
Did Devin leave at some point or
did he meet in the dad's house?
No, when we went out, I want to say
like it was a downtown area down there.
And we met him down there or whatever.
They just called by the Actons.
What is it?
Vine.
The street was called Vine and Actons.
Okay.
So we met down there,
whatever the case might be.
And after that, we went up, we went
out, we just chilled and went out.
And Devin had the gun the whole time
or he gave it to you at that time?
No, he had it the whole time.
And then when I wound
up leaving, I got it.
Okay.
And do you know if any other guns
were exchanged during that time?
No, I don't know about all that.
And you only came up with the one gun?
The one I had.
What kind of gun that was?
I think it was a nine, I think.
Nine, really no gun like that.
Okay.
That was my first gun.
Is that the gun that you
were later arrested with?
Yes.
You're positive?
Okay.
And Devin and Dion stayed down there?
Yeah, they stayed down there.
And you don't know if they came
back at that time with any guns?
No, I don't know.
And you only met whoever
it was that gave the
gun on that street and they had exchanged?
Yeah, they exchanged.
Do you know if they
exchanged money as well?
No, it was just a bag exchange.
Do you remember how he
passed the guns to him?
In a bag.
In a bag?
Yeah.
Like a double bag?
A double bag.
Did they talk like they
had done that before?
No, they just shot it up for him and then
boom, that's how the
car was set in the car.
He got in the bag, boom, he
got in the car and we left.
Okay.
Did you see that guy arrive in a car?
Yeah, he was already there.
Do you remember what kind of car he had?
I think it was white.
I want to say a white
Honda, I want to say.
Okay.
A white BMW, one of them.
It was white though.
And then how did you come
into possession of that gun?
Like when they got in the
car, did they give it to you?
No, I had it.
When I was ready to leave, when I was
ready to go back, he gave it to me.
He offered it or you asked to buy it?
No, I didn't buy it.
I was like, "Cousin, I like
that, let me get that."
He gave it to me.
That's nice of him.
I didn't buy nothing though.
Okay.
And then obviously he had other
guns in that double bag if they--
Yeah, I guess, yeah, I think so.
And brought it back up here.
Do you know how many
times that they've gone
down there and then brought guns back up?
They go back and forth
sometimes, for real, for real.
But I know that's how they get
them back on the Chinese bus.
And did they talk any more about
the guy that was buying them?
No, I ain't really discussed him for real.
You said in that last--I'm sure you
forgot because it was like a year ago,
a year prior, but the name
Rashard, do you remember that?
Yeah.
Who was that for?
The father.
But not the same person who
was exchanging the guns?
No.
I see.
And you said that Devin and Dion
are usually carrying guns on them?
Yeah.
Do you know who they're selling
to when they get back up here?
Anybody.
Do you know how much
they're making on the guns?
I don't know, probably about $1,000.
Per handgun?
Yeah.
That's a pretty good markup.
And do you know where they're getting the
money to originally buy them down south?
I think in profit from what
they make in offer, like a flip.
Yeah, and then they
just deduce the profit.
That's just from what I'm thinking.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Do you know how they
usually exchange money?
Is it like digital like
Venmo or is it cash?
I think it should be cash.
Cash.
I don't think it should be all
no cash happening out of there.
You would think.
Yeah.
And you don't know how many
times they've gone down there?
Do you recognize this person at all?
I don't know who that is.
Okay.
Do you remember what--and I guess you
didn't go to the gun store with him.
That was just a street.
In your phone, the phone
they took from you during
the search warrant that was
cracked and maybe broken,
do you know if any of the
messages or telephone numbers or
anything exchanged, anything
would be important in there?
No.
Nothing important in there?
No, not important in there.
I don't think they were
ever able to get into it,
but I also don't think that
they got a search warrant.
I don't know how you feel
about a consent to search.
I don't actually know that they'd be able
to break it, but I guess it's possible.
It's like a broken phone,
but we can always try.
A broken phone.
I think the screen was cracked.
It just didn't turn on correctly.
It just kept flickering on and off.
My phone won't crank.
Oh, really?
Maybe it's a different phone.
What kind of phone did
you have when you got it?
An iPhone.
This was an iPhone in a white case.
That's not my phone.
Okay.
I gave them my phone information.
They had my phone information.
I mean, it sounds like none
of the information would
be in the phone anyway, so
it's not that big of a deal.
The guy that was selling the guns, you
don't know how he's related, do you?
No.
Or if related at all.
I don't know.
Do you guys have any questions?
Did they ever ask you
about the gun afterwards
when you came back to
Baltimore to be honored, Devin?
No, they asked me about nothing.
They never said what happened to
it, even after you got arrested?
No.
I don't talk to none.
I don't talk to nobody.
What makes you think that that guy that
Devin and Dion got that gun from is the
same guy that purchased
them, or do you not know?
I say that because from just regular
conversations, we find
that this is us talking.
That's how it was brought up.
That makes sense.
Do you remember if the guns were in boxes?
No, they wasn't in boxes.
They was new, though,
but they wasn't in boxes.
You could tell that they were new?
Yeah.
You had mentioned something about
an AR, or like a long rifle.
Do you remember what that was?
I couldn't really understand
on the tape what you had said.
What you mean?
You said that they bring handguns, and one
time you knew that they
had brought a rifle up.
Yeah.
Was that during that trip?
Not the trip that I was on, but
prior to when they came back,
we was chilling one night
over at Nardi House, and they
showed me it, or whatever,
and they just got rid of it.
They sold it to somebody.
I see.
Do you know any actual
person that they sold it to?
No.
I don't really know the people.
They just sold it to people.
Okay.
I asked people that they knew.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I don't know.
Do you remember that
night, the date of that
night that you were hanging
out that they sold it?
No.
I just moved here.
I don't remember.
But you think that that
AR came from Georgia?
Yeah.
I ain't going to go to that on here.
Yeah, Maryland's pretty
tough to get a gun from.
Yeah.
Were you ever there
during a sale of a gun?
What do you mean?
Like were you ever present watching Deon
or Devin sell the gun to somebody else?
No.
Only that day I saw them
give it to somebody.
The AR?
Yeah.
And do you remember what
month that was maybe?
I don't know what month.
I think you were arrested in June.
You thought that maybe in May
was when you had gone down there?
Yeah, I went down there sometime.
I don't even remember for real.
I arrested, but it was
like, I don't want to
say like, I'm trying to
think of the weather.
You said it had been nice down there,
so they were thinking like maybe spring.
I don't want to say, probably spring
because it wasn't cold or nothing.
So probably spring.
All right.
And then the AR thing, did that happen
before that time that you went down?
No, it hadn't happened.
Okay.
I had gone down.
So between May and June?
Yeah, probably.
Yeah.
And you don't remember
who they had sold to?
Did somebody come to the house?
No.
No, we was out.
We was out somewhere.
I ain't come to no house.
Okay.
Nothing.
Did you say before you
were at Noddy's house?
Yeah.
Who's Noddy?
My homeboy.
You got out first last night?
No, I don't know.
It just called Noddy.
I got you.
Where's that house at?
Like over east, Erdman.
Erdman?
Yeah.
You know like, what part of Erdman?
I don't know the address of the apartment.
The host apartment?
Yeah.
Okay.
You remember what they looked like?
Was it like low rises, high
rises, like garden style?
Was it like a big tall building?
Were they small?
I mean, it was like the apartments.
Okay.
Yeah, it was like the apartments.
During any type of exchange
or even through talk,
do you think it was more Devin running
the show or Dion running the show?
I think it was more
Devin running the show.
And I guess Dion would be the
connect if it was down in Atlanta.
Isn't that where his family lives?
Yeah.
I guess Dion set it up and then
Devin would get people up here.
And do you know who
would handle the money?
No, I don't know what I like.
Okay.
Do you know if they're locked up?
I don't know.
Do you think that they would
still-- I don't talk to anyone.
I've been locked up.
I only speak to my family.
That's good.
All right.
Can you think of anything
else that I missed?
No, you got anything?
When you said the gun license, do you
know if that's like a license to carry
or just that they can easily
purchase guns down there?
I mean, if you got a gun
license, what is it for?
So different states have
different requirements.
So like in Maryland, sometimes you
have to have like a handgun license
to be able to purchase, you know,
or you can circumvent the system.
But sometimes if you have a handgun license
down in Georgia, you can just show that
and then you don't have to go
through different backgrounds.
I'm pretty sure if you got a handgun
license, then you can purchase a gun, right?
Right.
Usually.
But you never saw them
actually have a license.
No, I don't know about that.
Okay.
I can't think of anything else.
They were messed with like ghost
guns or P-80s or plastic guns.
I don't know about all that.
I don't know about guns.
That was my first gun.
I don't even play around
with them for real.
It was just for protection.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right, I think that's all I have.
[knocking]
[inaudible]
He's been relaxing.
[laughter]
[inaudible]
Is it pretty rough tonight?
Not really.
I've been like that before.
So you know the system all of it?
I'm patient with it, yeah.
Well, I know how healthy you've been after
this, and so hopefully
they see that, you know?
And especially I was listening to your
part of what -- the shooting situation,
so hopefully they understand that
that was not fully your deal.
It wasn't at all.
[silence]
Do you want me to watch
your eyes with the intercom?
No, you will not.
Sometimes the text
messages don't go through.
That's why I ended up calling back.
I was like -- because
I thought it was being
delivered on my end, but
it wasn't being read.
He just responded, okay.
Okay.
[inaudible]
All right, we'll go back in there.
And if you can think
of anything else as far
as gun trafficking or guns or violence
goes, we're always interested.
I will.
Get in touch with your defense attorney.
Okay.
Just letting you know
if you have some more
information, are you remembered
or, you know, anything.
Okay.
Just have your dad call
and say you need to see me.
Okay.
That would be out.
Yeah.
Because he freaks out.
No, he's worried about
his safety, which I told
him, Brandi, I told him,
I'm like, you just call me.
For him to call me and let me know.
But I told him, I'm like, I don't
think there's been an issue, but, yeah.
Okay.
He's always worried.
He called me at 10 o'clock last night.
[laughter]
And then he texts, he's like,
call me as soon as you wake up.
And when I woke up at 4:30, I'm like,
I don't think you really mean that.
[laughter]
You and I are different hours, I think.
He doesn't sleep.
He doesn't sleep?
No.
I don't know, I'd be
home, he'd be going out to
eat, watching TV or
something, or he'd just be up.
He doesn't know what's wrong with him.
He doesn't sleep, though.
Also, your family, like the most
supportive family I have of all my clients.
The whole family shows up
to talk, like all the time.
They're around you and out
there for you when you get back.
Yeah.
I miss them.
Do they come and visit?
Yeah.
Nice.
Yeah, they visit.
And they have video visits
sometimes too, right?
Do you have one of the toddlers?
Yeah, I got a toddler.
He escaped and next week is in person.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Yeah, I thought the toddler
thing was ingenious.
Yeah.
Thank you.
All right.
Go get your tea.
Thank you.
Do you need to catch up
with me at all, Brandy?
No, we good.
All right, okay.
Have a nice one.
Enjoy your lunch.
I will, you too.
Nice to meet you.
Same here.
We're waiting for your
food to come, Brandy.
Slide them up here.
Slide them down for you first down here.
If you can, let me get another cigarette.
Okay, I got you.
You need more water?
I think you're talking
to the wrong people.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
How many do you want?
Two or one?
Oh, yeah, two.
Silly question.
There you go.
Can I get you another pizza?
I'll be right back.
Give me a minute.
I'm sorry.