ff1 Like, literally, yeah, two and
three, just like four and three, yeah.
ff2 Exactly, so, in that moment, we-, it
will-,
they wouldn't have been able to maybe say
or explain many things
that they would have wanted
to kind of explain or explore a little bit
more, understand, but
now, we've spoken to them, you know,
obviously not all
seven-year-olds are the same,
or not all six-year-olds are
the same, but Oscar and Sienna
are very articulate, very,
very sort of communicative,
they've got a great relationship
with you, we've seen
it, I've seen it. I'm sure
Wanz and I have seen it too.
So, uhm, those are things that we look out
for.
We look out for, okay, you know, if
they've got a good relationship
with their parent or their safe parent,
then they will be able to feel confident
to tell their parent
something has happened.
ff1 Yeah. Okay.
ff2 So, yeah, so, those are
safeguards in place.
We will not be able to completely
take away the risk, mitigate the risk,
but we can manage it
safely for the children.
ff1 Yeah, as best as everyone can.
ff2 As best- ff1 And we just have to hope.
Yeah, we have to look forward
and it's as simple as that.
We can't, you know, otherwise, you drive
yourself crazy looking,
you know, in the past.
ff2 Looking back... ff1 Yeah.
ff2 And it doesn't mean that
if there's any worry,
this is why we give Oscar
and Sienna the education.
ff1 And the tools. ff2 And the tools.
And we give you as well the same education
and tools around things to look out for,
things to look out for in terms of,
okay, questioning, it's to
change this behavior,
to change how has this affected this mood
and all this stuff, things like that.
But it needs to be... Uhm, this is where
that's--
ff1 And I think it's really hard, even with
the, like, for example, at the moment,
the children, their
appetites are so, small.
And I'm like, is that
because of the hey-fee bit?
Is that, you know, just
some of your appetites,
even us adults, isn't that
appetite goes a bit less
and then you're like,
happy, there's a cold day. la1  ff2 Yeah, yeah. ff1
Tuck into a, you know, a big
hearty meal sort of thing.
So, then it's like, you know, it's so, tricky
because I think your natural instinct
is just to, there's a problem
and you're, not problem,
you know, there's an issue and then
you think, okay, then what could it be?
And you're constantly like, oh,
it's probably just the hey-fee, you know,
the coughing or whatever, you
just don't feel quite right.
Oh, you know, they're
coming to the end of a term,
you know, they're feeling
a little bit tired.
Oh, you know, they might just, you know,
I'm sure they'll start eating again
when they've gone through a growth spurt
and, you know, all of a sudden, you know.
So, like, you know,
they've gone from eating
like, almost like a large
chicken breast each.
So, where I always used to
buy a whole chicken and
basically we used to finish
that whole chicken together.
Like, you know, I'm only having to cook
like half a chicken now
and even that we had like...
so, we had half a chicken
and that was two meals.
It's just like...
ff2 "What's going on?" Yeah.
ff1 "Why are you not eating so, less?"
But then you see, but this
is the thing, isn't it?
You think, but like, you
know, you just think like,
okay, probably just the
sunshine, probably just tired.
And then, you know, sometimes children
have like, you know, two or three or,
it might go for a week or
week and a half of not eating.
And then all of a sudden-
ff2 They eat more and more.
ff1 They're like, "Mom, can I have
seconds?"
You're like, "No, I've just got
into making smaller portions
and not eating the same
food for three days."
ff2 Yeah, yeah. ff1 You know?
ff2 And you're absolutely right.
You're doing all of those things.
ff1 Yeah, so, it's quite tricky, isn't it?
Like, you know, even like
we're saying about size
and you're like, what's not,
like, you know, you could
ask me and I'd say, yeah,
that's not normal for them.
But then, you know, then you take into,
you know, everything into account.
ff2 And I think it's,
like you say, it's one,
you have to pay attention to
not just, I know one sign,
if their appetite has decreased,
it could just, like you say,
be a multiple of things, right?
But there needs to be more than one sign.
ff1 To pick up to some other ones.
ff2 Yeah, there needs to be more than
one, or like you've also, noticed,
and it could also, be
physical signs as well.
If you notice there was some,
maybe if your child was like,
"Oh, you know, all the
attention is doing this
to get around."
What's wrong with you around?
That kind of thing.
- But Sienna's very affectionate.
She just wants to sit on me.
She'll sit there and kiss me and kiss
me and say, oh, you don't pull my face.
And just kiss me and kiss me.
She loves it.
She's like really affectionate.
And she just like, she likes
really like strong cuddles.
She's like, squeeze me, squeeze me.
And I'm like, I can't
squeeze you that hard.
So, she loves like, like
if I'm sitting here,
she'll come in behind me and
say, "Mommy, lean on me."
I'm like, no, you'll get it.
- Because it's comfortable around you.
- But she likes it.
She likes that.
Whereas Oscar's a little bit,
you know, he likes his, you know,
like it might be different
between boys and girls.
Might be different between just like, you
know, just what they like sort of thing.
But anyway, I'm sorry,
you've completely gone off them.
- Oh, no, no, no.
I think to be honest, you
do know the right things.
You're obviously noticing
when things are changing.
for your children and you
are responding appropriately.
Even if you're sort of giving it time to,
giving it time to kind of let them sort of
come out of that funk.
And you are doing all the right things.
If you're not sure, you
take them to the doctors.
If not, you kind of see, okay, maybe,
but you can also, like you say,
if you see that they
change for the better,
but if you also, see another
sort of coupling sign
as well, maybe, you know,
irritable or something,
or like you will not wanting to get out
of bed, then actually those kind of be,
not indication about this, but indication
maybe they're not feeling very well.
- Well, you know guys, yeah.
- Yeah, I think that I know.
- Yeah, so, I put it down to the hay fever
because he is kind of like, you know,
I give him some of this Pyrites,
the children's one at nighttime.
And then sort of like, and then I think,
okay, then, you know, that stops.
But I can see when he
comes home from school,
it's the more of the coughing, isn't it?
- Yes, that's around now.
- Coughing, coughing, coughing.
And then, but you can hear it's like,
it's like a, not tickly cough.
You can hear it's a
different type of cough.
You can hear it in the
coffee, it's different.
- You do know the right things, you know.
So, in terms of their care
and how they're looked after,
all those sort of things,
that's not a worry for us.
If that was a worry, you know,
it would have been in the report.
So, there wasn't anything around that.
So, you know, the kids
are being looked after.
They've got a good relationship with you.
They are doing well at school.
They're having art therapy,
which is else to support.
They are having contact with dad.
- I've just remembered something.
- They're having contact with dad,
which is supervised, and
that's going really well.
So, that's not an issue right now.
And you are going back to court
and hopefully we'll seek mediation.
The thing that we'll
be looking to support.
will be to improve communication
for the benefit of the children.
So, I don't know what the
future is gonna be like.
Maybe the judge would say, yeah,
supervised contact should continue,
but it needs to sort of be
managed with the family members.
You already have your family
members already to plan.
- I've asked two friends as well,
but then they weren't clear.
I wasn't clear actually for them whether
they had to stay or what, you know,
to what degree and where
and stuff like that.
So, I was thinking, well,
you know, they've given
me a yes, but they've
got like more questions.
Like, do they have to
stay there the whole time?
- That would be a conversation for us
to have in terms of the network meeting.
If you can email me the details of- - Or
do they have to like, just a handover?
Like, will the time be constant?
- I think it will be tricky for us.
to really have some clarity on basically.
what that would look like until October.
Because you are going back to October,
you're going back to court in October.
And for the moment right now,
you've got something in place
in terms of CGC is in place until October.
But then what happens after October?
If the judge recommends
unsupervised contact.
or if the judge recommends
supporting contact,
or if the judge recommends that
contacts continue to take place,
or the judge can actually say, "I
want another assessment to take place.
I want another CAFCAS worker to come out."
And that's what we got from the CAFCAS
worker to say, when they go back in October,
I have recommended another
guardian, you know,
to take another assessment
or whatever it is.
So, we don't know what the
judge is going to say.
- So, what you've spoken,
so, what with CAFCAS now?
- I'm sorry?
- You spoke to CAFCAS now?
- No, no, no, in the assessment.
- In the assessment, in
the CAFCAS assessment.
Oh, if we go back to court.
Oh, that's if we go back to court before.
No, before October, in between.
- Are you planning to go
back to court in between?
- No, no, no, no.
The guardian that she's saying then
is if there's like issues
between me and Richard.
- Right, okay.
- Before the, so, we
were in court in March.
So, between March and
October, so, here in October,
so, while all of the visits happening,
if there's issues between us
and we can't figure things
out or there's like, you know,
then if we go back to court, then
there should be a guardian appointed.
- Okay, okay, that's fine.
So, that's fine then.
So, in that case, you've got your network.
I think we don't know what
that's gonna look like
come September, come October,
what the judge would say.
If the judge is wanting it
to continue to be supported,
then your friend's
brother will have to stay,
but they won't have to
interact with Richard.
They will just need to be in the vicinity
and just watch and just,
you know, just be around.
That's it.
But if the judge is saying, actually,
it can progress to unsupervised, you
know, and obviously getting the children,
like we said, this keepsake work
would already sort of be there.
and get them, Gauge their
understanding of it.
and all of those things like that,
then the children will be able to say
if they were ever, ever
at risk or in danger.
Does that make sense?
- Yeah.
- And that would just act like
a natural safeguard anyway.
And yeah, then it does be a case of, okay,
are we asking that the children
be collected from here?
That would obviously mean that Richard
is coming here to pick up the children.
How comfortable is it for both of you?
Is it really okay?
Is it really safe?
Maybe not.
Maybe we can ask your friend
to pick the children up
from here and take them
to like maybe somewhere
around the local park.
- Yeah, there's something there.
- And then Richard can pick them
up from the park or something.
I don't really know what
would be sort of the option,
but this could be things
that could be explored later.
I think if we'd like have a constant place
that we meet, I think that would be good.
Rather, yeah, yeah, but we don't know,
we don't know how it's gonna work out.
- Yeah, we don't know.
So, we're only speculating, so, please
don't hold me to ransom on that.
- Yeah, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I think sometimes I worry
about like saying things.
because like, yeah, like you might
feel that that's how I envision it.
It's like, but this is more
of like a sharing of ideas.
- Yeah, 'cause we don't know.
- Yeah, we don't know.
- And the judge, like I say,
has the ultimate decision.
Even if we recommended
that supervised contact
or supportive contact
needs to sort of continue
until the children are 10
or something like that,
the judge could actually
say, no, it's not feasible.
And he doesn't want that
or actually, no, it's not,
we've had that, we've had
that many, many times.
So, the judge, at the end of the
day, that's why he's a judge.
He sees all the evidences,
reads everything,
and he makes decisions or whatever it is.
If you're unhappy with
any of the decisions that
he's made, you can sit
to a lawyer and appeal it
or have a contested or
something, I don't know.
All of the things about your solicitors
or legal will advise you accordingly.
However, the hope is that
now that you've progressed
to where you are, children are
having some level of contact,
you should be able to come to
an amicable sort of agreement.
with Richard in mediation.
- To be able to, yeah,
I think the mediation,
that will like, I think that will help.
- Yeah. - Definitely.
Just two things while you were talking.
So, firstly, so, I know
we've got school as part
and I'd asked Mo to
answer this and she said,
no, we've got school, but I'll
ask you the question as well.
So, the children have private
tutors that they see once a week.
So, I don't know whether they should be
part of like this conference and like,
you can get more of an understanding
of like what Oscar and Sienna are like,
'cause then they see them
face to face like once a week.
So, they've got two
different private tutors
and then they've got another
one, so, they do this perform.
They absolutely love Dom and
Ria, they're like really.
So, I don't know whether you'd
want like input from them
or want them to be a part of
this conference and stuff.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Okay.
- Just to kind of follow up on what you're asking me. - Okay.
- And I'm not gonna make
that decision for you,
but I just wanted to kind
of have a think about it.
- Okay.
- How long have they had the tutors?
- One of them they've been seeing for about two years, I think.
- Two years.
- And the other one for about, Judith,
they've seen her since
about September before that.
No, I think it was September they
started, 'cause of this academic year.
- Okay. - I can't remember.
- So, one they've had about two years.
and one they've had about a year.
- Yeah, so, they say, yeah, and then, yeah,
Dom and Ria, they've had them
for about two years as well.
- What are their focus in
terms of, not the learning,
but in terms of the key
stage that they're teaching?
- What do you mean?
- So, usually when you
have a tutor, they teach,
so, like as education sector,
they're split in like
a key stage one, key stage
two, key stage three.
What is their focus?
Is it key stage one, key stage two?
Do you know what that means?
- Yeah, yeah, I know what
key stages means, yeah.
- Okay, so, key stage three is secondary
school, so, they're not there yet.
- No, yeah.
- But they're around key stage one.
- One. - Yeah, one.
- But they're going to two, yeah.
- Key stage two, when
they start to year three.
Now, teachers are focused
with different key stages.
Sometimes if you're a
teacher in a primary school,
you can only teach
reception at key stage one,
when you teach key stage
two, and that's it.
You might not be able
to flip between the two.
That was ages ago, like before 2007,
you could flip between the two.
But after 2007 or 2008, you
couldn't flip between the two.
You had to pick a
specialty or pick an area.
So, I'm asking because at some point,
does the teachers will change?
Or would they not change?
You don't know.
- I don't know.
But then I know with Judith, I
think she tutors um, what's it?
So, stats is the school one.
11 plus is the one that they
get into grammar school.
So, I know she does the 11 plus as well.
- She's doing some part of key stage
two or just the 11 plus because--
- Oh, she's doing parts
of, yeah, well, yeah.
I could ask her.
I don't know, actually.
I shouldn't really-- - Ideally, we
will not recommend the private tutors.
because that's something that
is in the home environment.
And you will be in the home
environment with the children.
But the children are outside
of the home environment.
Hence, when they go to school, that's
why we work better with school.
- Right, okay, okay.
- Does that make sense?
- No.
(laughing)
- Okay, so, you are the one that employed--
- Oh, 'cause I employ them.
- Yeah, you employed them.
You're paying for them.
- You can tell bitches that you wanted.
You wanted Nafi to pay half.
(laughing)
- I'm joking, I'm joking, I'm joking.
- I'm staying out of that one.
- I'm joking, joking, joking.
No, no, no.
That's just me joking.
- Yeah, I understand.
But that's the basis.
So, school is independent.
- Independent.
- And we work with independent--
- Independent people.
- Yeah.
- Oh, because I've been employed there.
- So, the police is independent.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I see, I see, okay.
- So, the only person
that could come is Karen
with whom you're saying
is your support network.
But that person is there to support you.
- Right, okay.
- Not for the children.
- Right, oh, I see, I see.
- Right, so, that's why when
we did the scaling question
in my meeting, I didn't ask her to scale
because it would have been inappropriate.
for her to scale on the situation of
your family because she's supporting you.
- Yeah.
- She would have probably
scaled to favor you.
Doesn't mean that she would, but
she would, you know what I mean?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, I get it.
So, it's that, so, that's
the, see, but then you see,
it's like, it's so, nice
that you're able to, like,
like, so, if I've got a question,
you're able to articulate it
and come back with a response
that kind of, like, tells
you, yeah, like, basically
they're not independent.
So, like, you know, if they
did, or, you know, yeah.
Okay, that makes more sense.
- But I like to talk
because I'm still here.
- Yeah, same.
But then, like, so, my, but then, like, you
know, people that they
see on a regular basis,
I suppose they have their own
training and stuff, isn't it?
- They will, I mean, they will.
- So, maybe if they have gone, yeah.
- The thing I just want
to consider is that
because they see Oscar and Sienna at home,
they don't see them outside of the home.
- They see them outside
at their, at their.
- At the school.
- Not the school, so.
- At the facility.
- Yeah, the facility.
- So, they will have their own
safeguards in that school.
- Okay.
- They are never really alone.
They are with other people
within that facility.
- And then they have,
yeah, so, with Judith,
they have, they see Judith at her
house and they see Simon at theirs.
And then Ria and Dom, they
see in this Methodist church
just over there, and that's
like their perform thing.
And then tennis, like, you know,
it's not really one-to-one.
It's like with a whole
group and they're outside.
- If there was a, if there was something
that we're looking to get, so, for example,
because it can work
differently in the form of,
let's say, therapy, so, you
are seeking, you're seeking,
you're getting support for your
mental health with therapy.
and you wanted, you know, and
maybe it was a private therapist.
So, private therapists,
you often pay for that.
We will not be inviting them to a meeting,
but we will seek where you
are in terms of your need.
You know, are you taking your medication?
Are you having regular reviews?
We don't need to find out
what you're discussing
'cause that's obviously doctor,
patient, privilege or whatever that is.
But we just wanna know that your
mental health is being supported.
Does that make sense?
- Yeah.
- With this aspect of care, the
children are having additional lessons.
It's not anything that would be relevant
to safeguarding for them.
They can only give the opinion about,
okay, what they're special, okay,
Oscar is doing well in maths,
Oscar is doing well in English,
Sienna is doing well in English,
you know, and vice versa.
But school can as well
give an indication of that
because that's their main base.
This is extra tuition.
But at the same time,
you have to also, consider
the other aspect that
should we be asking them
their opinion around what Richard is,
Richard might not really value us sharing
that part of his information
with somebody else that
doesn't do anything else
other than tutor the children.
I don't know if that makes sense.
But the school looks after
the tutoring of the children
but they also, look after the
wellbeing of children as well.
Does that make sense?
Like you are focused
on not really tutoring
but wellbeing of the children in the
home or you do homework with them.
So, some level of not tutoring
but some level of education work.
School does, the other-- - Constant education
at home, I tell you, it is constant.
- You tell it doesn't stop.
- You know what we've started doing,
they have this weighing
thing, oh my God, right?
So, now we weigh everything.
We weigh the toast, the
bread in the morning.
I'm like, please, I need to put
the scales that are weighing.
- You just drop something
out from them, that's it.
- He's like, oh, mummy, 47
grams for a slice of bread,
that's really light.
I'm just like, well, just
put it in the toaster now.
- So, you see the difference.
So, they won't be able to
give any clear indication
about how the children present
in the home because they
don't really know anything
other than the learning.
Or maybe they can say that.
- So, the reason I say is
just because they spend
like one to one time, an hour,
about 45 minutes with them
and then, you know, and
even the other ones.
is like an hour and a half and stuff.
But like, it's--.
- Don't get me wrong, if Oscar
made a disclosure to them,
they have a duty of care to tell us
in terms of how they'll report it.
And then, because it came from them,
we would invite them to
the meeting at that point.
But before that moment,
because we are having all the information
that we require in terms of from school--
- No, no, no, I think it's like,
I think, yeah, like you said,
like school is independent,
police are independent,
you're independent,
everybody's independent.
And then, you know, then
you're gonna have, you know,
I think questions could
be raised, like they're
like paid tutors by you,
so, you're employing them.
So, therefore, what they say may, could,
not that they, not that what they would say
would be anything different
if they weren't independent.
Yeah, but like, I suppose if
you could raise a question
Mark over it, it's probably
just not a good thing then.
- Well, it wouldn't, yeah.
- It makes, it makes, yeah, no, no, okay.
- And I think the other
question then would be,
if we're asking, because
with other people,
we have to ask them and they have to
be able to offer something in return.
So, like school, we are
saying, well, where are they?
Can you offer something in return?
So, like Elsa support and all those
stuff like that, somebody is doing that.
With your tutoring, they
wouldn't be able to offer that
because that eats into
their tutoring time.
So, then it becomes a therapy session as
opposed to actually just academic learning.
So, there isn't really like much, doesn't,
not in a bad way, but there's not really
much use for them other than the tutoring.
- That's fine, okay.
And like, so, I suppose I should ask CGC.
I don't know whether, so, like, you know,
just when you were talking,
so, I was thinking like CGC,
if they haven't got, but
then in the court order,
it says CGC, I was just
thinking, like, do you know, like
from now until, just to make
it easier for the children
so, that they could have
it in the community,
like locally rather
than going to, you know.
- We can email them.
- Have you got, like, have you, no,
have you got like supervisors
that you guys use?
- Oh.
- Like a company, but it's just, I'm just thinking,
I'm talking out loud now, but in
the court order, it does say CGC.
- We only use our contact centre.
We do have a contact centre.
- But they don't have people that are
employed there that do
that kind of stuff, no?
- We do, but only for cases
for us in our court arena,
not for private proceedings.
So, 'cause you've got private proceedings,
it wouldn't fall under our jurisdiction.
We would not be able to
even comment on that.
- Oh, okay, that's fine, that's fine.
I just thought, like, so,
like the way I see it is,
if CGC can't accommodate,
let's look at, like,
potentially a different
option that we could,
like, just to make it
nicer for the children.
Like, it is a bit of a mission,
like going all the way
up there and coming back,
but then obviously, happy to
do it, don't get me wrong,
but just like for the children, I think
it would just be nicer if it wasn't
like a long drive there, a
long drive back sort of thing.
- I think you might raise
it up again with them
and see if they can accommodate
somewhere a bit closer.
- I'll find that thing with
the, with the price of it.
- And double check the cost
as well, so, that they're
not gonna say, oh no, because
you only paid 80 pounds,
you have to bring the
child to Basingstoke,
and then you know for sure that actually,
that's the reason why
you're going to Basingstoke.
But just get some clarity from them.
- Yeah, but you know, it
clearly states that it was,
I don't know, it's just
sometimes you just think,
people have been doing it for so, long,
like now I really wish it had said,
but then actually that was
it, yes, I know, I remember
now, because in the last,
what do you call it?
When we were at court, there was that, in
the, I don't, it wasn't in my statement,
it was something else, yeah?
So, basically saying that
perhaps Richard might wanna,
like I suggested things to do, because
they'd only been going to the arcade,
and they'd gone to golf at the arcade,
and so, I just wrote down to be helpful,
like they could go to Windsor
Castle, go on the duck tours,
they could go chocolate making,
they could go ape, and made
suggestions like that, in and
around here, what they could do.
And then, and then, yeah.
- Sorry, I'm not in that.
- I'm just thinking that like, yeah,
'cause I made the suggestion saying,
these are the things that you
could do in and around here,
so, I'm just, so, what my thing is,
like I wish like in the court order,
it'd been more specific about,
the supervision has to be,
like more here, or easier
for the children to get to,
rather than me having to go to
Basingstoke, Basingstoke was
only supposed to be, if the
supervisor couldn't come here.
So, but then it's not, reading through
it, it's not really stipulated that well,
but now I kind of, yeah.
- I think maybe this is something that,
like you say, you've reflected
on in hindsight,
is maybe if you did go back to
court, you would have to bring,
did you represent yourself,
or did you let a solicitor?
So, then maybe you want to bring it to
the attention next time or something,
hopefully it doesn't, we
don't know what it's gonna be,
but if that was ever a case then,
because then you'll be saying,
for future you would like contact
to kind of, be in this area anyway.
- Yeah, but then I remember
him saying, 'cause he was like,
that's really controlling, she's been
controlling, she's been controlling,
and I was like, actually
I'm just trying to be helpful
and give suggestions that would be things
that the children might like to do,
that would be a bit more
child focused, but if you
feel that it's controlling,
like, you know, it's like,
I can't take anything
about it, then can I?
'Cause I genuinely just
trying to be helpful
and find things that the
children might want to do
that you might not have thought
about, but yeah, anyway.
- But that's-- - And then I
think I was so, focused on being,
don't be controlling,
like he thinks you're being controlling,
that I suppose I didn't like--
- Pay attention to the other stuff.
- Pay attention to the other stuff
and just let it, and was just
like, right, okay, I don't want
to appear as controlling, so.
- Is that, so, in terms of the journey,
I think this could be a
reflection point as well,
you could maybe explain
what the journey is.
to the solicitor at the time, to say
it's 40 minutes to go, 40 minutes to come.
Sometimes, you know, I don't
know what the journey is.
- But even like getting the children
downstairs, come on then, let's go,
right, get your shoes on,
get this on, da-da-da-da-da,
just that whole even getting ready
before you even get out the door
is like, you know, a good like
15 minutes, 20 minutes as well,
so, door to door, like, you know,
from the minute you start saying,
come on, we have to go now, come
on, come on, get your shoes on,
fifth time, come on, get your
shoes on, then you relax.
- Definitely, it's definitely,
yeah, it's worth
exploring, I'm sorry, I'm going
to have to make my way.
- No, I get it, no,
that's fine, thank you.
- I hope that was okay for you, if I
sort of answered the other sort of stuff.
- That makes, yeah, it all
makes, makes a lot more sense.
- Sort of begin the work.
So, my colleagues should be in touch
in terms of doing some keep safe work,
I know, right, I'm just awful
at this, keep safe work,
I just speak more slowly,
that will probably help.
- Look, I'll show you some things that
the children did, this is like over the,
this was the last holiday,
not the holidays just now, but
they went to get, Sienna had
her birthday party on Sunday.
- Oh, happy birthday, Sienna.
- But this isn't her birthday party,
this was Theo's birthday party,
and she got the idea from,
look how high they are.
- Oh, wow.
- That's like 25, 20 meters or something.
- Wow, that's lovely.
- Really high, we went to see the crown
jewels, they took this book into--
- Where was this, in London?
- Yeah, the crown jewels, the Tower of
London, so, that's, we took them there,
then they wrote like, you know,
I saw the crown that King Charles
is going to wear on the coronation,
so, we actually saw that crown,
and Oscar actually traced that, the
tracing paper, how cool is that?
- Very nice.
- Good, isn't it?
- And my favorite crown was the
tiny one, made for Queen Victoria.
- Oh, wow.
- So, she was like,
and then we seen Queen Victoria's crown,
there's a picture of her, where am I?
- They look like they had so, much
fun when they had the outing.
- Yeah, and then they had, you know this,
this ring, they showed it in
the coronation, and this ring.
- Okay.
- And this was the crown.
Then we went to, that's my mum.
We went to see, we saw
the soldiers and stuff.
- Does she live around here?
- No, just Hayes, just
down the road, not too far.
And then we went to see,
oh, we just went round,
and saw pictures of the
coronation and stuff.
And they'd see, when they saw the police
on horses, they thought that was amazing.
Went on cable cars.
- Yeah.
- That was really good, that
was at the O2, that was amazing.
- Very nice.
- Went to a birthday party,
and then when kids see
like butterflies and
stuff, they really love it.
And then, yeah, went to Southampton
Marina with some other friends.
They thought this was amazing.
- Yeah.
- Saw the deer.
- And when the deer was crossing the road.
- They thought it was so, I was so
happy, I could not believe my eyes.
- No.
- At Sienna.
I saw the deer crossing,
and crossing the road.
It was the most wonderful sight,
and the best experience of my life.
- Oh my goodness.
- And I was like, that's in my life.
- Ah.
- Everything's my life.
I went clip and climb,
I think it was a birthday party.
Amelia's seventh birthday party.
Went to Bushy Park.
This, how cute is this?
Look, I went to Bushy
Park, I saw brown bark,
I saw some deer, there's nothing to fear.
I went in the sand,
and it was squidgy land.
- Oh, very good rhyme.
- How cute is that?
- What a poet.
- So, sweet.
And then like, they made these, they
haven't written that out, their bits,
but they made these, a flamingo and
this, and you have to put the beads in,
and do those things.
- Very nice.
- And I thought those bubbles were nice.
Sienna's class is Hadid class,
and this lady, Zahra Hadid,
she builds like curvy buildings.
- Oh right.
- So.
- So, it looks like you had
lots, lots of fun activities.
- Yes.
I ran out of printing ink.
- For the picture.
- For the, no, not ink, the paper.
So, I've got some more paper and stuff.
So, Richard.
- The Little Mermaid.
- Oh, it's really good.
Have you seen it?
- Yeah, I went to see it.
- Oh, so, nice, isn't it?
And Richard got these magazines, the week.
- Life Savers.
- Juniors.
- Very nice.
- So, they didn't ask
me what vaping was, I
said, "Never you mind,
"read the other bits."
(laughing)
- That's funny, but you know what,
that's them being inquisitive.
- Yeah.
- So.
- And I'll definitely have more and
more questions for you as time goes on.
- Yeah.
- So, I think,
teach them everything in moderation.
- Yeah.
What's the, when's our next, so, is our
next, are you coming to see the children?
- Yes, I'm coming, I think.
- Is it next week?
- I think next week, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- And I'll do some work with them.
- Okay.
- Around what we've been
discussing this Tuesday.
Keep safe, what, my goodness,
like I can't help myself, can I?
So, keep safe work, we'll
do some work around that.
And then, somebody in my team is gonna
come and do some work with you around,
you know, what are the
signs, what to expect,
and then some more keep safe work.
And when I, yeah, I know
I got it right this time.
And when we eventually
sort of step away from your
family's lives, then you can
continue that keep safe work.
And there will be some resources as well.
So, resources meaning like places
you can explore or look online.
- Yeah.
- Around,
and tailoring it to their age.
- Yeah.
- So, right now, we can't
all obviously talk so
explicitly about sex and
all the stuff like that.
But we can obviously do
little things about, okay,
when they touch you, this is
just face, you can say no,
all those kind of things like that.
If you've got a safe
person to talk to, you talk
to mommy, you talk to
the teachers at school,
you can talk to auntie,
you've got your worry bear,
and there's a thing that
we'll show them as well.
Or you've got, it doesn't have to be, it
doesn't really have to be a worry bear.
It can just be, you can write a
letter, you know, or like a diary.
And you can sort of, you know,
I don't know whether you get
like a little, made out of a
cardboard, and can post it.
- Yeah.
- And forget the worries, you post
it, and later you can read it.
So, it's a very fun activity to do.
- Yeah.
- If you can, or even like a
shoe box, like a memory box.
You can keep a shoe box, you can
write like a little note in there.
You don't really have to
physically go and buy worry bear.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause that, I am-- - Now, what
we've got is-- - My mom's house.
- Remember when I said--
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- It was like, mommy it doesn't work.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, alright.
- A shoe box, you can
fold it up, and put it
in a shoe box and stuff,
and read it later.
- Okay, so, just, I just
said that, so, I think,
I think these hand balloons
from the party, I've just,
they're sort of dwindling, but
I just put them there for like,
you know they just like to see them,
until they're just like, sorry we digress.
So, yeah, so, I think you're seeing them
next week, I'm sure it's in my diary.
And then somebody else has
got to contact me, yeah?
- Yeah, come from my team.
- That's fine.
- If not, I will do some work
anyway, before she comes,
she's our practice social, not social,
she's our practice assistant in our team,
so, she's not a social worker, but
she's like a practice assistant,
so, she's supporting social workers,
because as you can understand, we have
other, other families that we support.
- Yeah, so, something that you could, yeah.
- So,
- Yeah, to lighten your load,
but you know what I mean, yeah,
so, to do the stuff that,
they don't, that you can,
- Yeah, so, I could do
the work, but I wouldn't,
I wouldn't give you all
that time that you need,
like all the attention that
you need, so, like right now,
I can come maybe once a week,
but she can even do every day,
that kind of thing like that, so
we'll just sort of work on the plan,
and she will contact you at some point,
and yeah, - Okay, good, all right,
then I'm gonna write that
email to Claire again.
- Oh yeah, and if you can email
me your network support, and then,
the people that want to be, and then I can
sort of have, we can have that meeting,
if we work best, we can do it on
Teams, or we can do it at your home,
everybody will be here, if they
can't be here, I can come here
and be with you, - So, you're gonna
do this before October?
- Yeah, before October, whilst
we're still, so, we can discuss what,
so, like you said, your sisters
were having some questions,
but you didn't know
what that would entail,
so, we can at least have their viewpoints,
about what their commitments would be,
and what that would look like, to
understand what it could entail,
and then come October, you
can present it and say,
well this is my side of the
list, and Richard will have his
side of the list, and then
we can kind of work that way.
- Fantastic, so, that's what
you can do, perfect, okay, bye.
(door opening)
(door closing).
(footsteps).
(footsteps)
(door closing)
(door opening)
(footsteps)
(footsteps).
[BLANK_AUDIO].